Lindley, Christopher Papers /3013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Christopher Lindley Papers
1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lindley, Christopher
/3013
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Papers regarding various ILR School Extension programs.
3071975
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 19, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Biographical / Historical
A graduate of Cornell University (PhD, history), Christopher Lindley was Senior Extension Associate at the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
College administrators.; Adult education; Lindley, Christopher.; Doherty, Robert.; United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3071975
- Scientists and Engineers: Personal Problems and Issues, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "The 'New Management' Finally Takes Over", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Business Week
- The Impact of Human Resources on Business (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Notes & Quotes
- Master of Science in Building Systems Design (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Attitude Change, Behavioral Change: The Role of the Training Department (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Insight from Labor Relations (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Trends Which Will Influence the Future of Personnel Administration (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Management of Personnel Quarterly (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Basic Objectives Which Shape the Character of a Company (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Training as a Change Agent: A Constructive Evaluation (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Management and Professional Development (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notes (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Discussion Leader's Guide for Sessions on Industrial Relations and Labor Relations, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Robert Merry Comments on "Centralized vs. Decentralized Control", 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Economics: Our Standard of Living, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Elements of Administration, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  1 of 4
- Elements of Administration, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  2 of 4
- Elements of Administration, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  3 of 4
- Elements of Administration, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  4 of 4
- City of Rochester - Inter-Departmental Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Solid Waste Management in Central New York, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Anderson
- ILR Memorandum and Charts (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ILR Records (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ILR Records (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Work Experience Program (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Monroe County, New York
- University Labor Education Association, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Evaluative Methodology (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ILR Seminar (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Questionnaire Forms (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Scratch Paper (Box 1, Folder 32)
- The Challenge of Hope The Challenge of Hope (Box 2, Folder 1)
  1 of 2
- The Challenge of Hope (Box 2, Folder 2)
  2 of 2
- Ed Chambers File (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1 of 3
- Ed Chambers File (Box 2, Folder 4)
  2 of 3
- Ed Chambers File (Box 2, Folder 5)
  3 of 3 '
- Health (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Continuation of Education (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Community Action Skills Development Project (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Community Action Skills Development Project (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Community Development Training Project (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence from and to Bob Doherty (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence from and to Bob Doherty (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Risley Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Chris Lindley (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Clippings & Articles (Box 2, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 16)
- School Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Bert E. Swanson (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Community Action Leadership Development Program (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Community Action Leadership Development Program (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Community Action Leadership Development Program (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Community Action Leadership Development Program (Box 2, Folder 22)
- State Education Department Federally Aided Programs (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Politics, Community Organization, and Full Options (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Community Action Skills Development Project (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Final Evaluation Report
- Block Assembly Project (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Auburn Action Group: Rules, Regulations, and By-Laws (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A Proposed Housing Study and Plan for Low-Income Housing (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Auburn, NY
- Research/Training Proposal Submitted to the Economic Opportunity Program, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Appendix #11 Elmira Public Housing Survey (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Appendix 12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Appendix #14 Geneva Project Help (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Report to Project HELP on Certain Organizational Issues: Alternatives and Consequences (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Appendix #15: Process for Organizing a Tenant's Union (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Amendments to Community Action Skills Development Project "A Program Proposal", 1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Preliminary Training Proposal for Board of Directors and Advisory Councils, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- A History of Neighborhood House (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Elmira Neighborhood House, Inc. Organizational Chart (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Council of Community Services of Chemung County, Inc., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A Program Proposal - Submitted to the Office of Economic Opportunity, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Application for Community Action Program (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence with John C. Rober, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- U. S. Department of Housing and Urban Renewal Handbook, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Transmittal Notice No. 83
- Community People Work Sheet (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Cornell University
- Buddy Training Program (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Buddy Training Program (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Instructor's Buddy Training Manual, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Buddy Training Manual, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Greenleigh Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Greenleigh Associates, Inc. Expense Reports, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- University Labor Education Association (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Puerto Rico Urban Renewal and Housing Corporation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Copyright and Publication Procedures (Box 3, Folder 31)
- State of New York - Travel Voucher, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- State of New York Travel Voucher, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- State of New York Travel Voucher, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Human Resources Development Institute (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Considerations in Employing the Disadvantaged in the Job Program (Box 3, Folder 36)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Community Services Committee
- Instructor's Manual for Training Buddies (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Jobs in Industry for "Hard Core" Unemployed (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Toledo, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Memorandum and Workshop Sessions, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Discussion Leaders Ideas (Box 3, Folder 42)
- The Harry Lundeberg School of Piney Point, Maryland (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Human Resources Development Institute (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Report of the Sub-Committee on Community Service (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Notes on Urban Affairs Program (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Educational Activities and Community Conditions (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Extension and Public Service Division (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Politics, Community Organization, and Full Options (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Community Affairs Program Proposal Summary (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Proposal to Provide Specialist Utilization, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- NY State Education Department (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Peasant Society and the Image of Limited Good (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Materials & Publications (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Proposal Submissions (Box 3, Folder 56)
- The Engineer (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Justice Detained (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Guidelines on Personnal Mobility (Box 3, Folder 59)
- A Plan for Court and Probation Services (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Your County Monroe (Box 3, Folder 61)
- ILR Cornell University, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- ILR Cornell University, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Breakdown of Federal Assistance to Wayne and Monroe Counties During 91st Congress (Box 4, Folder 2)
- In-Service Training Program (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Community Action Skills Development Project (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Board and Advisory Council Community Action Training Project (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Board and Advisory Council Community Action Training Project (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Board and Advisory Council Community Action Training Project (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Reports of Division Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Reports of Division Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Job-Oriented Human Relations Training, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Memorandum ILR, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Lindley-Swanson "Reciprocity of Change" paper (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Chapter IV The Reciprocity of Change: A Case Study (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Bert Swanson - Disadvantage Approaching Majority: Mt. Vernon (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Chapter I: From Social Maintenance to Social Change (Box 4, Folder 15)
- The College and the Community: Evaluation & Design for Planned Change (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Citizen Participation (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cooperative Extension, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- NY Industrial Education Center (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Concerted Services in Training and Education, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Title I Grant (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Title I Grant (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Title I Grant (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Title I Grant (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Title I Grant (Box 4, Folder 25)
- US Department on Housing and Urban Development (Box 5, Folder 1)
- US Department on Housing and Urban Development (Box 5, Folder 2)
- US Department on Housing and Urban Development (Box 5, Folder 3)
  3 of 3
- Manpower Development (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Unions (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Urban League of Rochester (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Adult Education (Box 5, Folder 7)
- The Challenge of Hope (Box 5, Folder 8)
- The Challenge of Hope (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Labor and Urban Crisis (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Labor & Management (Box 5, Folder 11)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 12)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 13)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 14)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 15)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 16)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 17)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 18)
- ILR School Memorandum (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Business Cards and Address Index (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Adult Education (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Adult Education (Box 6, Folder 2)
- ILR Faculty Memorandum (Box 6, Folder 3)
- ILR Faculty Memorandum (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Extension Employees (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Extension Memoranda (Box 6, Folder 6)
- ILR School Planning Committee (Box 6, Folder 7)
- ILR School Planning Committee (Box 6, Folder 8)
- ILR School Memoranda to Extension Staff (Box 6, Folder 9)
- ILR School Memoranda to Extension Staff (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Correspondence: General (Box 6, Folder 11)
- The Community Union for the 1st Ward Lackawanna (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Community Union for the 1st Ward Lackawanna (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Community Action Training Program (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Rochester Programs (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Rochester Politics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Office of Regional Resources and Development (Box 7, Folder 6)
- OEO Proposal (Box 7, Folder 7)
- OEO Proposal (Box 7, Folder 8)
- OEO Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Tioga County (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Weinberg Reports (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Weinberg Reports (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NYS - OEO (Box 7, Folder 13)
- NUEA File (Box 7, Folder 14)
- New Jersey Community Action Training Interview (Box 7, Folder 15)
- National Welfare Leaders Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 16)
- NAB Proposal (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Monroe Co. Human Relations Commission (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Ext. Personnel Comm. (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Essex County (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Extension NYS Agriculture & Home Ec. (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Clinton County (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Center for Cooperative Action in Urban Education (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Local 2603 Lackawanna (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Hanover Houses Tenants Unions (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Greenleigh Associate (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Greenleigh Associate (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Gates-Chili School Program (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Fulmont Development (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Ford Foundation Project (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Extension Staff Meetings (Box 7, Folder 31)
- ILR - Varieties of Work Experience, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Harold L. Wilensky
- Elmira Housing Project (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Elmira Housing Project (Box 7, Folder 34)